<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Dr. Henry Naiken.Msc.D]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Dr. Henry Naiken.Msc.D]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 05:44:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The human mind functions within a certain field. You will go beyond that. There is nothing in the unconscious that you have not seen before. Your mind works only within the boundaries of the field of whatever you have previously heard, seen, thought of, or imagined. This is the field of the phenomenal world. Patanjali says you can cross that field. Your mind wanders within a boundary of its own, but it can go beyond. You are not aware of that. There is a way of training your mind and all the various faculties of your mind so that you can go beyond. There are many other fields where mind gets freedom from all these forms, and remains in a state of joy and happiness. “Beyond” means the transpersonal field. The field of your personal mind is small. When you know that this field is not able to help you, then you cross to the transpersonal field. Then you will find that you receive help, and you can help yourself in a better way. Self-confidence is important, but it is also essential to take help from the transpersonal mind. You will cross the mire of delusion and go to the kingdom of spirituality, the kingdom of light, where pains and miseries will not affect you, and you will be in a state of constant joy or bliss. A human being can do that.</p>]]></description>
            <link>undefined5797f764-0974-4ef8-9473-d295eb83a767/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5797f764-0974-4ef8-9473-d295eb83a767</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2016 05:44:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>